待っていた
I've been waiting for that sun to shine endlessly, without wavering.
迷いなく輝き続ける太陽
I've been waiting for those clouds to drift through the blue skies!
待っていた
空の青を食いぬいたような雲
I've been waiting for the freedom to sleep in as late as I want!
待っていた
朝寝坊を自由自在な毎日
ついに来た
It's here.
It's here!
ついに来た
ついに来たんだ
It's finally here!
夏休み
Summer vacation!
Hey!
おーい
It's so hot.
あつ
yappari kimi da yo ne
Oh hey, it's you?
honto odoroita yo
You startled me
futari yoku aruita namikidoori
Here we are, on the tree-lined road we walked so often
otona ni naru no wo
I couldn't wait to grow up, and kept you at a distance, didn't I?
mattezu ni toozaketeita no wa atashi datta ne
itsumo
As always,
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
the icy rain falls
kimi ga kureta namida
comprised of tears you cried for me
sono yasashisa made wakaranakute
That kindness I didn't understand
zutto kono mune wo shimetsuketa
lay heavy on my heart all the time
mainasu ichido no ame ga furu
The icy rain falls
tsumetasugiru namida
comprised of tears unbearably cold
hagurakasu taido ni okotteta kedo
Although I was angry at my evasive personality
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作,仅供学习交流之用
若您喜欢本作品,请支持正版影像制品
---诸神字幕组---
日听：バサラ  翻译：景寒筱
校对：慧慧 AL  时间轴：葛蔓  压制：PHENOTYPE
jitsu wa sukuwareteita n da ne
you cured me of that, didn't you
Let's play!
遊-ぼ-う-
Impossible.
無理
What?
I have a bunch of people to save.
なぜなら
俺には今救わねばならない人々が大勢いるからさ
People to save?
人助け　何？
What? Yukki, are you doing volunteer work?
祐希まさかボランティアーとか
I guess.
まあね
大金で動く男じゃありませんからね　俺は
After all, I'm motivated by more than just money.
What's this? An incident?
おー　何　事件？
Yuuki, if you don't hurry it up, they'll all die.
祐希　早くしないと皆死んじゃうよ
そいつは大変だ
We can't let that happen.
What did Chizuru want?
千鶴なんだって
さあ
Who knows?
Go home.
帰れ
I haven't even said anything yet!
まだ何も言ってないんじゃん
I already know what you want.
聞かれなくてもわかったんよ
That makes things easy!
だったら話は早い
What do you want to do? Where should we go?
どうする
どこ行く
Hey, where should we go?
ね　どこ行く
I'm told you that I'm not interested in going out!
だから遊びなんか行かねえっつの
俺今課題やってるの  じゃあな
I'm busy!
See you later.
Wait.
待ってください
Just one minute. Just talk to me for one minute.
一分　一分でいいので
You have a minute to talk, don't you, ma'am?
話だけでも　話だけならいいじゃありませんか　奥さん
これ使えば　お肌つるつる　これ
This'll make your skin silky-smooth.
What are you, a door-to-door salesman?
お前が営業なんか
はい
Coming.
Oh, Chizuru-kun.
あれ　千鶴君
よく家が分かりましたね
I'm surprised you found your way here.
今暇
Are you free? Do you want to go out?
遊び行かない
Huh? Um, well...
そう…ですね
You can't, either?
春ちゃんまでダメか
Oh, that's not what I meant.
いいえ　そうじゃなくて
そうですね
Let's see...
Would you like to join me?
じゃあ　一緒にやりましょうか
一緒に？
Join you?
What's this?
これは
I was making snacks.
お菓子作ってたんです
I've never done it before,
ほとんどやったことなかったんですけど
but since we're on vacation,
I thought I'd give it a go.
休みだし  やってみようかなあって
Would you like to help me?
一緒にやりません
Why not?
まあいいか　やろうやろう
Let's do it.
Oh, good. Can you mix that dough for me?
よかった
じゃ　そこの生地混ぜてもらえますか
これか？
This?
Yes.
はい
Chizuru-kun, you're good at that.
千鶴君上手ですね
Huh?
またまたそんな　僕なんてまだまだですよ
There you go again. I'm still learning.
That smells good.
いい匂い
本当ですね
It really does. I hope it turns out well.
おいしくできるといいんですけど
Tastes about right.
こんなものかな
Shun-chan, that's no fair.
春ちゃんばっか狡い
ああ　ごめんなさい　はい
Oh, sorry.
Here.
わー　甘くてふわって口の中で広がって おいしいです
It's deliciously sweet and light in my mouth!
I look forward to seeing how they'll turn out.
出来上がり楽しみですね
Me, too.
そうですね
Once we're finished,
we should take them to...
じゃあ　出来上がったらこれ皆のところにも
What is this strange feeling?
It's like I'm not really myself...
何だ
今の異空間は
俺が俺でなくなんって気が
Um...
あのう
Are you bored?
飽きちゃいました
でもここまで来たから 最後まで作らないと
Now that we've come this far,
we should finish making...
作る？　新しい俺を
Making what? A new me?
はい
What?
You wanted someone to hang out with,
どこか遊び来たくて皆の家を回ってたんですね
so you went to everyone's houses.
That's right. It's summer vacation,
そうだよ
せっかくの夏休みなのにさ
皆って涼しい部屋に籠っちゃって
but everyone's hiding in the cool air of their rooms.
It's really hot today.
今日特に暑いですからね
でも１カ月もあるから
But there's a whole month ahead of us,
so I'm sure there will be opportunities to play outside...
きっと外で遊ぶことも
あっ　じゃあ
What about a festival?
お祭りなんかどうですか
A festival?
お祭り
There's one today.
今日あるんですよ
夜なら結構涼しいし
It'll be cool at night, and I'm pretty sure everyone would go if I invite them.
誘えば皆も来るんじゃないかな
What do you think?
どうします
Shun-chan, thank you!
春ちゃん
ありがとう
Thanks to you, I think I'll have a wonderful summer vacation!
君のおかげで　すっばらしい夏休みが送れそうだよ
Everyone should have their own Shun-chan.
やっぱり持つべきものは春ちゃんだな
おかげで幸先のよい夏休みがスタート
Thanks to him, I can start to enjoy my...
あいつ
It's her.
Hey!
I can't believe they didn't have anything smaller.
こんな大きなしかないなんて
That looks heavy.
重そうだな
Need help carrying it?
持ってやろうか
I'm fine. Leave me alone.
いいわよ　ほっといて
お前な
You should learn to accept others' kindness...!
人の親切っていうのは素直に受けておいた方が
She looks like a sheep.
なんか羊みたいだな
Oh, here it is! The invitation to the festival!
来た来た
祭りのお誘いか
えっとー　皆さんの都合はいかがですか
Let's see. "Can everyone make it? Let me know."
返事ください
Of course I'll go!
行くに決まってるんじゃん
Hey, what about you?
な　お前は
な　おい
Hey!
Shun-chan invited me to a festival.
春ちゃんからお祭りに誘われた
そんな夏の始まり
That was how our summer began.
おー　日本のお祭り
A Japanese festival!
なんで浴衣姿なんだよ
Why are you wearing a yukata?
It's a festival, you should to wear a yukata! It's refreshing!
祭りと言ったら浴衣でしょう　いきじゃないすか
祭りと言ったら雛でしょう
Shouldn't you buy a baby chick at a festival?
買っちゃダメだよ
Don't buy one. Our apartment doesn't allow pets.
マンション動物禁止だから
ああ　より取り見取りですね
There's so many to choose from.
There's so many that I don't know where to start.
本当
より取り見取りすぎて
どこから行くかも迷っちゃうぐらい
I know, right? I can't decide, either.
ですよね　迷っちゃいますよね
なんかおなかすいた
I'm hungry.
Let's get something to eat.
そうだな　適当に食うか
適当だと
"Something"?
ダメだ　適当は
No! Not just "something"!
As students, we don't have a large budget.
俺たち学生は予算が限られている
If we don't carefully and precisely choose the right food stall, we'll regret it for sure!
高騰する屋台の食べ物を慎重かつ適格チョイスしないと
必ず後悔することになる
でもいろいろありすぎて
But there are so many choices...
I don't know what to pick.
何を選んでいいのやら
Calm down!
落ち着け
In a situation like this, start with the classics! First off, we'll go with...
こういう時はまずは定番から
初戦は
たこ焼きじゃん
Takoyaki!
Hey.
Why don't we all buy something different and share?
皆で１個ずついろんなものを買って回し食いした方がいいんじゃない
なるほど
I see.
Good idea, Yuutan!
さすが悠太
A high schooler who knows his festivals!
祭り高校生
そこまで称賛する作戦か
Is the plan that praise-worthy?
This is delicious.
おいしい
本当ナイスーアイディアでしたね
That was a really good idea!
Yes, but...
そう　でも
Yuuki!
祐希　いい加減　回せよ
Pass it around already!
Don't worry, you'll have your fair chance...
心配しなくても機会は均等に回ってくるよ
いずれ
...eventually.
A fight breaks out every time we buy something.
買うたび争いが勃発してるけどね
How long are you gonna hold on to that?
あんたいつまで食べてんのよ
Don't worry. I'll eat it so you don't get fat, Mary.
安心しろう
太らないように 俺が食ってやるよ　メリー
あ メリー
Mary?
Oh, yeah. Her hair's kinda fluffy, like a sheep's.
そう　なんか髪の毛が羊っぽくぶわぶわってしてるからさ
A sheep?
羊
Masaki-chan?
茉咲ちゃんが
そんなことない
That's not true!
Ow!
いてー
What was that for?
なんだよ
Masaki-chan, where are you going?
茉咲ちゃんどこ行くんですか
あっ　いやー
Oh, um...
あー　可愛い
So cute!
They really are.
本当だ
小さい頃ほしくて　よくやったんですけど
I really wanted one when I was little,
なかなかうまく取れなくて
but I could never get one.
すばしっこいんですよね　金魚って
Goldfish are so quick.
はい　春ちゃん
Here, Shun-chan.
Thank you, Masaki-chan.
ありがとう　茉咲ちゃん
よし
All right!
Here you are.
はい　嬢ちゃん
Take your time, Miss.
慎重にな
You going for it, Mary?
挑戦するのか　メリー
Now!
今だ
Wait!
待って
Miss, you don't know what you're doing, do you?
嬢ちゃん　尻が青いじゃねえのか
It rips! That thing rips!
破れるっつの　そりゃ破れるっつの
Here's your consolation prize.
はい　残念賞
Hey, Mary.
メリー
I thought I could do it.
うまくいくと思ったのに
おい　メリー
Hey, Mary.
まあまあ　そんなしょげるなよ
Don't get so down about it. You almost got one.
メリーにしては惜しかったって
Don't touch me!
触らないで
いて
And why do you keep calling me "Mary"?
大体メリーって何
Don't give me weird nicknames!
勝手に変な宛名つけないでよ
Stop it. Cut it out.
やめろう　やめろうって
Just leave me alone!
もう　ほっといて
That hurt. I came to cheer you up.
ちぇー　慰めにきちゃったのに
ったく可愛くねえ
You're not cute at all.
Is Masaki-chan okay?
茉咲ちゃん大丈夫ですか
I can't help her.
もう手が尽きられません
茉咲ちゃん
Masaki-chan.
Forget her.
やめときなんて
If you get close--
近付くと
Leave him.
ほっとっけ
Here.
はい　どうぞ
Shun-chan.
春ちゃん
残念賞ということで
Think of it as a consolation prize.
I'll treasure it.
大事にする
大事にするね
I'll treasure it!
What was that about?
なんだあれ
She gets super mad at me,
but treats Shun-chan like that.
俺にときはきーって怒っといて　春ちゃんにはあれですか
Well, sorry, but I'm not any good at cheering people up.
はいはい悪かったですよ　慰めが今一で
She doesn't laugh with anyone except Shun anyway, right?
あのな
あいつはもともと春以外は笑わねえだろう
行くぞ
Let's go.
Is that right?
ああ そうだっけ
それじゃまるで春ちゃんに恋…
Sounds like she's in love with...
Huh?
あれ
What?
What?! Is she?!
ええ そうなの
水面下でそんな恋のメロディーがあったなんて
I didn't hear the melody of love bubbling beneath the surface!
It's not underneath the surface. It's obviously above!
水面下というより
水上に出まくりバレバレなんだけどな
Really? So that's why she...
そうなのか
それであいつ
She's not cute at all.
可愛くねえ
What's the matter?
Are you boys rookies, too?
どうしたどうした
兄ちゃんたちも青尻か
ごめんね
Sorry.
しょうがないよ
It's okay. This paper's too thin
to catch anything that's alive.
命あるものを扱うには薄っぺらいもん　この紙
まあ　そこを逆にゲームとして使ってやれって狙いだろうし
I'm sure that's the point of a game like this.
I feel like it shows no respect for their lives.
命を軽視しすぎる気もするけど
Hush.
シ　価値観人それぞれだよ
Value is subjective.
こんな生き物を弄ぶような商売
His business is making a game of their lives.
Don't you agree?
ねえ
You And I
What a generous man.
や　気前のいいおじさんだったね
紙５重ねにしてくれるなんて
I can't believe he gave us five layers of paper.
金魚取りすぎて返しちゃったよ
I caught so many goldfish that I had to return some.
大方　お前らがそうするように仕向けたんだろう
I'm sure you did something to make him do that.
しかしどうして春ちゃんなんだ
But why Shun-chan?
この中じゃ一番男っぽくないっていうか
He's the least manly of all of us, and like, more cute than cool...
格好いいというより可愛いというか
むしろ顔だけでいったら俺の好み
In fact, if we're just talking about his face, he's my type...
いえいえいえ　そういう話じゃなくて
No, no, no! That's not what this is about!
What are you mumbling about?
何ぶつぶつ言ってんだよ
But...!
だってさ
理由なんか本人にだって分からねえもんだろう
Sometimes, you don't even know why you like or dislike someone.
好きとか　嫌いなんっつの
Shun-chan!
春ちゃん
茉咲ちゃん
Masaki-chan!
ほれほれ　群れ中羊っぽくね
Doesn't she look like a sheep in a flock?
Shun-chan!
あー　確かに
She does.
More importantly, we should help her.
じゃなくて　助けてあげなよ
要
Kaname?
Hisako, you're here, too?
日紗子
来てたのか
Yeah.
Onee-chan.
お姉ちゃん
Onee...
お姉
Oh, Kaname-kun. So you're here, too.
要君　来てたんだ
Yeah.
食べる
Do you want some?
Onee-sama!
お姉さま
I'm Kaname-kun's friend, Chizuru.
僕要君の友達の千鶴って言います
どうです　この後花火でもやりませんか
Would you like to set off some fireworks later?
素敵な夜をお約束しますよ
I promise it'll be a wonderful night.
Fireworks?
花火
When did you make that plan?
いつそんな計画立てたの
ないよ　花火なんか
We don't have any fireworks.
If love always went according to plan, heartbreak wouldn't exist.
恋が計画通り進む白物なら誰も胸を痛んだりしないさ
スーパーにならあるんじゃないですかね　花火
They should sell fireworks at the supermarket.
確か近くにあるんで　僕ちょっと行ってきます
I think there's one nearby, so I'll go check it out.
じゃ　あたしたちも行こうか
Should we go, too?
そうね
Okay.
But...
でも
It's okay. We were just saying it'd be nice to get out of the heat.
いいのいいの
そろそろ涼しいところ行きたいなって話してたところだから
そうですか　じゃあ　お願いします
I see. Thank you.
春ちゃんは
Where's Shun-chan?
The three of them are going shopping for fireworks.
花火買いに行ったぞ
三人で
What?
It's okay. Don't get flustered.
大丈夫　焦っちゃダメ
I have the keyring that Shun-chan gave me!
こっちには春ちゃんからもらったキーホルダーが
It's missing!
ない
Masaki-chan.
茉咲ちゃん
Do you want to come with us?
茉咲ちゃんも来ますか
Uh, no. I'm fine.
私いいや
Really? Okay.
そうですか
It should be around here somewhere.
確かこの辺のはずなのに
Sorry.
ごめんなさい
Excuse me.
すみません
It's okay. Don't get flustered.
大丈夫　焦らないで
もう一回あっちの方から
I'll just start from over there again.
何してんの
What are you doing?
Don't go off by yourself, Mary.
ちょろちょろどっか行くなよ　メリー
Oh, you dropped something.
あ　落し物
えっ　まじか
Seriously?
Leave me alone!
ほっといて
何強がってんのよ
Why are you acting so tough?
What am I gonna do with you?
しょうがねえな　俺たちも探して
We'll help you look—
I didn't ask for your help!
いいから　余計なことしないで
Listen, an attitude isn't going to make your flat chest—
あのな　お前可愛くないのは胸だけにする
Let's go, Yukki! Forget her!
ったく　行こうぜ　祐希
もうしゃん
一人で探せるんなら
If you're going to search by yourself, try not to look so upset.
あんまり周りにべそ顔見せないようにね
Right after I said not to...
言ったそばから
Mary.
メリー
What is that?
何それ
So, you want us to help look?
で　一緒に探せってか
Fine, but...
まあいいけど　それより
Why are you so beat up, Chizuru?
なんで千鶴ぼろぼろなの
Ask her.
こいつに聞け
７００円もしたのに
It cost 700 yen.
It's pretty crowded from here to the shrine.
でも　ここから本殿までの間とはいえ
この人通りだからな
It won't be easy.
結構手間だぞ
Let's split up and search.
皆でばらけて探しますか
Sensei! The class is trying to work together,
先生　クラス一丸となろうとしてるのに
but Yuuta-kun isn't participating seriously!
悠太君が真面目に参加してくれません
悠太君　女子の体育が気になるのも分かるけど
Yuuta-kun, I know you want to look at the girls outside in gym class,
but you have to put some effort in now.
やる時はやる
You, too.
お前もな
Sensei, I found it.
先生　見つけました
Found what?
何を
Seriously?
マジですか
Hey, shorty. Is that really it?
おい　ちびこ　本当にあれでやってるのか
What is it, little girl?
なんだ　お嬢ちゃん
間違いない
That's it.
あのう　その熊さん私が落としたものなんです
I dropped that bear. Could I have it back?
返してくれますか
That? I found it.
これか
これはな　おじさんが拾ったんだよ
And she's the one who dropped it.
だから　その落とし主がこいつで
Do you have any proof?
証拠は
はい
What?
If you don't have any proof, you can't have it.
証拠まねんならやらねえよ
But, I said...
いやいや　ですから
If you want it, shoot it down.
ほしけりゃ　撃ち落としはいいだろう
300 yen per round.
一回３００円な
I'll never grow up to become that kind of adult.
俺絶対こんな大人にならない
More like, you'll never become that kind of person, right?
っつか　こんな人間にはならねえっだな
拾ったものを景品にする時点でアウトだね
I can't believe he'd make something he found a prize.
Thank you—
毎度あ
You idiot!
ど　大バカ
I can't believe you let your emotions get to you!
お前いっとけの感情で
Let go!
放して
Calm down.
落ち着けますって
そうだよ
That's right.
If you get emotional,
you won't be able to aim properly.
感情的になると命中率が補注
You're too calm about this!
お前らは落ち着きすぎだ
しかたねえな
Fine.
I'll do it.
ここは俺が
All right.
よし
こらこら　全力で頑張った人を笑っちゃダメだよ
Hey, you shouldn't laugh at people who are trying their hardest.
要は全力でやってこれなんだから
That was Kaname's best effort.
You're not helping.
ほろになってねえよ
You can do it, Yuutan!
頑張れ　悠太
This might be hard with such a small target.
これは確かに的が小さい分　難しいかも
That's right! It's not easy! Right?
そうだよ　むずかしいんだよ　な　な
For something like this...
こういう時は　やっぱり数々なミッションを突破してきた彼でしょう
We should rely on someone who's cleared countless missions before.
Well?
どう
The size of the target doesn't matter.
的も大きさは問題じゃない
やられる前にやる
Kill or be killed. That's all that matters.
それだけの話さ
It's not that serious.
そんな重い話じゃねえよ
What are you aiming at?!
何狙ってんだ　こら
幸せは一つに絞りませんでした
I couldn't choose between them.
まったく祐希は
I don't believe you, Yuuki.
And now we're out of bullets.
しかも　今ので玉なくなっちゃったんじゃん
There's nothing we can do.
しかたねえな
They got the fireworks, so they're coming back.
春たち花火買ったから　戻ってくるって
Shun-chan's coming back.
春ちゃんが戻ってくる
落としたってばれちゃう
He'll know I dropped it!
Old man, I need some bullets.
おやじ　玉だ
What?
You're already paying with bills?
お前いきなり札が
So much for saving money by sharing food.
皆で食べ物１個ずつ買ってた意味がない
If I get it, you're paying me back, Mary.
落としたら後で返せよ　メリー
Whoops.
ありゃ
You're one to talk.
あんま人のこと言えねえな
Shut up.
お黙り
1 round (5 shots) 300yen
Damn it.
くっそ
どうした　兄ちゃん　あと一発だぞ
What's wrong? You have one shot left.
I know!
分かってますかな
Should I take over?
代わろうか
You stay still.
お前はいい
Damn it.
くっそ
Who said I could do it if I fired enough shots?
誰だよ　下手な鉄砲数うちゃ当たるなんて
これじゃ金の飛ぶ流し
Now I'm just wasting money.
Namu... Namu... Namu... Namu...
南無 南無 南無　南無 南無
Here.
ほれ
Thanks.
Why is a young girl like you chanting, "Namu, namu"?
っつっかさ　年頃の娘が南無南無って祈り方はどうなんだよ
But maybe that's why I managed to hit it.
まあ　でもそのおかげで当たったのかもしれねえし
いいか　な
Who knows, huh?
You're right.
そうね
They're back.
春たち帰ってきた
We're back!
ただ今
Welcome back!
お帰りなさい
なんだよ　取ってやったのは俺だっつの
We bought fireworks.
I'm the one who got it back.
Amazing. There are so many.
We have more!
She's not cute at all.
可愛くねえ
Let's fire them off together later.
後で皆でやりましょうね
Yeah!
Should we save the sparklers for last?
線香花火はやっぱり最後ですかね
If you get too close to me,
俺に近寄ると火傷するぜ
you'll get burned!
You're the one coming towards me!
お前が近寄ってんだろうが
Chizuru-kun, that's dangerous!
千鶴君　危ないですよ
As the fireworks gently nudged back the night,
花火がほんの少し夜を弾くと
そこにいつもの笑顔があって
everyone's smiles were there as always.
A firework's glow is short lived,
花火の輝きってのは明けないもんね
お前の人生のように
just like your life.
If you don't stop playing around, you'll get hurt!
もう　ふざけてると火傷しますよ
I can't believe they'd mess around like that.
まったく　ふざけるなんてとんでもない
Wielding fireworks is a serious contest.
花火持ったら　真剣勝負ですよ
違うでしょう
No, it's not!
I never thought the time would come when I would sometimes softly open my hand
当たり前のように手のひらに上で増えていく日々を
いつまでも大切に握りしめては
時々そっと開いてみる
to look at the ordinary days that I'll treasure and hold on to forever, accumulated in my palm.
そんな時が来るなんて
Look over here.
はい　こっち見て
A photo with just me and Shun.
春ちゃんとツーショット
Here we go!
はい　取ります
That looks fun.
楽しそうだな
お姉さんもそうぞ
Go right ahead.
遠慮しないで　楽しんでいってください
Don't hold back. Go enjoy yourself.
What?
That's not what I meant.
そういうことじゃないんだけどね
I probably won't realize it until I'm an adult.
それに気づくのは
きっと大人になってるから
One Summer
僕は泣き虫で　悔しくて
boku wa nakimushi de kuyashikute dakedo
It pains me to be such a crybaby,
だけどあなたに今伝えたいんだ
anata ni ima tsutaetai n da
but I want to tell you my feelings right now
tada massugu ni boku wo mitsumeru tsuyokute
There you stand, silently gazing at me
ただまっすぐに僕を見つめる
強くて優しいその瞳に応えるために
Giving me the chance to answer you and the strength and tenderness in your eyes
yasashii sono hitomi ni kotaeru tame ni
itsushika miushinatteta ichiban taisetsu na mono mo
you taught me about what I lost sight of
いつしか見失ってた
一番大切なものも
sotto anata ga oshiete kureta
that was most important to me
そっとあなたが教えてくれた
tashika ni sou omoeru kara
I have no doubts about that
たしかにそう思えるから
boku wa yowamushi de iya datta n dakedo
I hated how weak I was
僕は弱虫で　嫌だった
だけどもっともっと強くなるから
motto motto tsuyoku naru kara
but I will continue to become stronger
anata no koto mo mamoreru you na boku ni naru kara
I will be someone who could protect you and me both
あなたのことを守れるような僕になるから
dakara sukoshi mattete
so wait a little longer for me
だから　少し待ってて
Glasses and Et cetera
Next time: Glasses and Et cetera